SQLite高效的查询能力  使得数据行的删除  更新和插入都变得容易许多
Using SQLI makes it easy to delete, update, and insert rows using highly
你甚至可以在修订数据库时插入新的列
expressive queries. One can even add new columns as you revision your database.
所以受欢迎的应用都会或多或少的使用SQLite数据库并不奇怪
It's not a surprise that just about popular app makes some use of SQLI to
它是Android解决方案中十分受欢迎的重要元件
Android. It's a very popular and important component of the Android solution.
Android还提供了大量的帮助函数使得使用数据库更加容易
Android also provides a huge set of helper functions to make working with
包括数据库的自动查询与建立
databases easy, including functions to automate query building.
支持ListView显示的查询甚至是编译语句
Display ListView is populated by queries and even compile statements. For
要获得更多关于Android数据库的信息  可以查询用户手册
more information about databases in Android, see the instructor nodes. One thing
我要提的一点是我们教你的是在Android中建立数据库和content provider的基础方法
that I wanted to mention is that we're teaching you the fundamentals of how to
这是因为一旦你学会了这节课
build database in a content provider on Android. The idea is that once you
你会很好的理解整个过程是如何工作的
are done with this class, you'll have a good understanding of how it all works,
即使将来你只是使用函数库建立数据库
even if you end up using a library to help build your database and
和content provider
content provider in your future applications. That's it for
这是对Android存储的概述
a brief intro into storage on Android. If you want to learn more,
如果你想知道更多  到developer.android.com网站然后搜索数据存储
go to developer.android.com and search on Data Storage.